Amanda Steele Show. We are on a group chat Thursday joined by our headliner of the week,
Michael Collier. When do you know a relationship is getting serious? Now you've been married for
178 days. How long was the process before day one? I don't know if there was a process. She was,
you know, she was just the one when I met her. She was just, I mean, I've never had this happen.
In fact, I was done with relationships. I wasn't in no more relations. I was done. The last one
was brutal. In fact, she was a vegan and she was a brutal vegan. Like if I'd be eating chicken,
she'd be like, oh, I see you're having caucus today. I'd be like, yeah, I'm putting some barbecue sauce
on that caucus. So I was pretty much done, except my wife walked up to me and invited me to the soul
food restaurant. You're going to get me every time on that one. We didn't have that normal courtship
because we sort of knew we were the one. You know, I mean, both of us were married twice and divorced.
Like by day three, I knew that I was in love with her by the third week because I called
everybody who thought they had something to do with me and told them to call me.
You know, just leave that, lose that number. I wrote a text. I wrote a text to a chick
I used to see that I met some cutie fine with who I want to be.
By the second month, I stopped objectifying women and I've objectified women my whole life. I mean,
I could be one another woman. Look at that there. Look at that here. I wanted to see. Now,
I wouldn't care who you are. I mean, I know Beyonce and Rihanna. I've met them both, but they could
both be standing in front of me butt naked with two hands full of hundred dollar bills. All I could
think about is stone.